Welcome back.
I want to go to the zoom terminals before we do anything, because I want to see exactly what happens when you fill them all out.
This is the fairy gate.
This way.
I gotta go to the library.
Upstairs there's a zoom terminal.
We can use that to teleport.
Down here.
Go up.
And I think we had some zoom terminals in the first region that we didn't complete.
If I'm not mistaken.
Down here.
Over here.
Probably there was a zoom terminal closer by, but whatever.
Actually, hold on a minute.
What happens if I go down here?
Did I take a shitty way?
Ah, I could have just gone here.
Wait, how does that actually make sense?
We go in here, and then we go upstairs.
And then we're here?
Huh?
That actually makes no sense if you think about it.
Ah, but I guess we're going upstairs.
Never mind.
We're using a staircase.
Okay, sure.
I can see that.
Uh, go.
Okay, so which ones have we not done yet?
This one and that one.
But it looks like there's one final one up here.
Look.
So it's pretty much confirmed, I think, that the next level, whatever it is, is going to be the last.
Which is also why I want to do this before I open this machine up here.
Big things are no doubt going to happen, and I still have mysteries to solve.
Let's go here.
Uh, yeah.
And then click on this guy.
Let's see then.
We should be able to translate all of this.
The alchemists want to help the monster.
Yep!
They want to heal it!
They want to cure it!
Okay.
The alchemists...
Uh, what do they call the alchemists up here?
Not impure, that's devotee.
The alchemists.
Not chosen ones, those are bards.
Bellman.
Scientists.
That's the one.
Okay, so the scientists want to help the monster.
And scientist in plural is plural.
Scientist.
Uh, help the monster.
Want to help monster.
I think we had a glyph for want to.
Unless I'm mistaken.
Uh, come on.
Make... Wait, wait, wait.
Scientist.
Yeah, yeah, seek want.
Seek to help the monster.
Now, where's help?
Oh, there it is.
Help.
Monster, which, uh, but in this case, they call them impure.
But there's a disconnect of communication here.
The warriors are going to think that the scientists, or the alchemists, want to help the devotees, which is not actually the case.
I don't want to miscommunicate this.
Do we have another word for monster here?
Nah, probably not.
Okay, just do it.
Yeah, okay.
The alchemists are afraid.
Yeah, I would be too.
Those monsters are scary AF.
Uh, okay, so plural.
Scientists.
Scared, or fear.
Yep.
The alchemists don't want to die.
Well, that makes sense.
Scientists do not...
Uh, not seek, or seek not to die.
Probably not seek.
Not... want...
death.
Death, death, death.
Warriors don't fear death.
Where is death?
There it is!
Warriors are not afraid of the impure.
Okay.
Okay, dude.
Sure.
You seem very afraid, though.
Okay, so warriors, that's plural.
I think they also call them warrior, right?
Yeah, warrior.
Plural.
Not afraid of the impure.
So, not...
Oh, God.
I can never find my way around this.
Okay, that one we need.
Not.
Okay, so warriors... not...
fear...
the impure.
In this case, monster.
And where exactly was that?
Uh...
monster.
There.
Warriors will help the scientists.
Nice!
Everyone is getting along.
I like that.
Warriors...
are going to help.
Uh, help, help, help.
Where is that?
Help...
How about wait?
Will... want to... seek...
We may have to throw that in there.
Yeah, we definitely do...
Where is it?
Seek, want...
Help, scientists.
Ah, but wait!
Scientists is pluralized, dammit.
Okay, we gotta... that's wrong.
We gotta do it again.
Warrior...
Warriors... now we just do help.
And of course I already forgot where that was.
God dammit.
There.
Help...
scientists.
And the scientists are where?
Oh my god, this... I wish I could search through these.
Alchemist.
Plural.
There we go.
And...
Oh, we're almost fully connected.
Something has changed.
What is this going to create in the end?
I don't know what, but it's gonna look cool.
Uh, okay, okay, okay, nice, nice.
Let's go here.
So, something in the warrior domain and something in the alchemist domain has changed now.
Gotta go check that out.
I wonder who's winning this game of whatever that game is called.
Oh, what am I doing?
We have to interact with the terminal.
That was the whole point.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, the devotees are speaking to the alchemists.
Help me.
You help me.
You...
Why is this one so difficult?
Shouldn't you be one of the first we found?
Am I crazy?
Ah, there it is.
You help me.
Help me.
There we go.
Plants are dying.
Ah, of course they would seek the alchemists for that.
Uh, plants.
Wait, do we have a word for plant?
In this language?
Oh, we do!
Okay.
Plants... dead.
Uh, monster, death dead.
There.
I don't want plants to die.
I believe you.
Uh, I, so me, don't...
so not...
I don't want...
seek...
Where's my seek?
Slash want.
There.
I don't want plants to die.
And plants is pluralized now.
Death.
Oh, God.
Where was death?
There.
Boom!
Nailed it.
He has an idea.
Look at him.
I will help you.
Oh, yeah?
Ah, of course.
Now we have to speak in devotee language.
So weird seeing these symbols again.
It's been a while.
They look so primitive compared to the other ones.
In a weird way.
Uh, I will help you.
So I...
Uh, let's see.
That's you.
Where's I?
Uh, warrior, preacher...
What?
You help.
Oh.
I help you.
Help was one of the later ones we found, I think.
Or maybe not.
God, I spent so much time just going through this.
You.
There.
Okay.
I will create a formula.
Nice.
Electrolytes.
It's what the plants crave.
I told you from the beginning of the game.
Remember when I took on the role of the preacher?
And I spoke to the people and the church.
I told them of the electrolytes.
I spoke the truth.
I think I missed my calling.
I could have been a great alchemist.
I create formula.
What is formula in this language, though?
So, me, create...
Create...
Where are you?
Make, create, formula.
What could that be?
Let's think about this.
Could be a potion.
In this case, you know, they could see that as a potion.
Let's see if there's a better alternative.
Before we pull the trigger.
No, it's got to be a potion.
Yeah!
I shall make a potion for you.
Ooh, look at that, look at that.
Oh my God, that's so cool.
We're gonna see alchemists here.
I gotta look.
Hey, yo!
What's happening here?
They're still vibing to the music up there.
What's happening down here?
Okay.
What is going on inside of the abbey here?
Are we still in sneaking mode or...
We are!
Come on, I helped you guys so much.
You're not gonna let me pass?
Are you forcing me to sneak around like a thief?
Maybe this guy will let me in now if I talk to them.
Open up!
It's me!
Idiot.
Okay.
I love this view.
This is what inspired the thumbnail for this series.
This view right here.
Oh, the cat!
We gotta go pet the cat.
Pet it.
There you go, look at that.
That's a good kitty cat.
See you later, cat.
I was expecting some alchemists to be here, but okay.
Maybe they are somewhere else.
We could try going...
I don't even know where to go here.
This way?
Where we came from?
Wasn't there something else down there?
No, there wasn't, but we can teleport.
I also forgot where this door is supposed to be here.
Let me go here.
That one doesn't have any puzzles to solve, but...
still...
I think this leads to the graveyard.
But my memory is very foggy on this area.
Ah!
There we go!
Very nice.
That's not what I want to do, though.
I want to go over here.
I wonder how this game plays with the controller.
I think it plays really well, actually, except the writing part.
Right.
Let me see what's over here again.
Is this the nice view?
Oh, look at that!
There they are!
He's so thankful!
Look at how he's clapping his hands!
The potion is working!
The formula is in effect.
You love to see it.
Another cat!
Why can't I pet that cat?
Okay, let's head upstairs here.
I like these little details here.
It's nice!
I want to find that one view...
where people were playing games.
Oh, but wait!
That was in the bard area, wasn't it?
Maybe I'm...
messing up the areas in my mind here.
Wait, I never walked here!
Oh, I didn't realize you could go around like that.
Okay, he's still vibing to that song.
Yo!
Look at that!
The slaves are sharing food!
What is that?
Is that food?
I'm just stepping on his coins.
We're seeking the preacher, go to the garden.
Preacher loves the garden.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to see what's happening inside the church.
Are they allowing foreigners inside their holy grounds?
Brothers!
The electrolytes have arrived!
Of which I spoke earlier.
We have communicated with the alchemists and they have created the ultimate formula.
Plants are being revitalized.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
No, I don't want to walk in their line.
I just want to get out.
Just that way.
I know it seems like I'm just sort of wasting time in this game right now, but I enjoy going through these areas and just seeing what changed.
It's a lot of fun to me.
What was this way?
Right.
Wait, where are the people walking?
Okay, there they are.
And this way is...
Oh, this is where they create pots and all that, I think.
Wasn't it?
All right.
Okay, we don't need to go that way, I don't think.
Let's get back up.
I still don't understand where this door is.
Oh, is it over here?
This very hidden door that needed a special entrance key.
This is not it.
It may have been in the very first area, actually, now that I think back on it.
And this place is so peaceful, look at that!
This slave is making miniature model ships.
And the devotees are completely taken aback.
Look at that, they love it!
Yay!
That made this whole trip over here worth it.
Just for that, that was nice.
The sharing of culture here is cool.
And the bards do have a fascination with boats, right?
They make these very cool looking...
Well, helicopter boats, you can almost call them.
This is the place where we saw the key with the little boy.
Okay, I want you to catch me.
Hey, look at me.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Can you catch me in time?
Go, go, go.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Oh, you're too slow.
You're too slow.
Wow.
I guess I could have always just done that.
Seems much easier.
Okay, let's go up here.
No, no, no.
Wait, I think I know where the door is.
It's somewhere close to here, I think.
Uh, maybe down here.
No, it's not down here.
This is where the murals are.
I bet I'll find it later.
I don't have the key for it anyway.
I need something very specific in my inventory, right?
Uh, no, let's not do it this way.
I am going to use the terminal.
You know, it's kind of fitting, calling them zoom terminals, because you can do zoom calls.
And you can also zoom around the world with them.
It's the perfect term for that.
It's the perfect terminal.
Haha, everything comes together.
Okay, let's take it to the top.
Let's do the, uh, the addition.
I'm pretty sure I know how it works.
I fucked it up last time a little bit.
Uh, wait, this way.
No, wait, did I come from...
Oh shit, I'm already lost.
Look at the map.
So we're here.
Okay, up.
Even though it's kind of north and up, it's weird.
That map is weird as hell.
But so is my brain.
It's a bad cocktail, guys.
Uh, okay.
Oh no, it reset what I did, I think.
Didn't I have something here?
Shit.
I forgot what I did.
That's okay.
Let's just, uh, review.
Here.
Okay, so we need, uh...
So this is gold, silver, carbon.
Gold, silver, carbon.
And copper apparently is already done.
Right?
Okay, so we need, uh, 1,405.
1,405.
So that would mean we are going to need...
1,000, but wait, we don't have a 1,000.
We have to add...
500.
Oh wait, I think I did it wrong last time.
500, that's 1,405.
That's 200.
Uh, that's 300.
405.
And what was that?
Gold.
And gold looked like this, okay?
Which is that one.
So now I do...
Okay.
Okay, very good.
Now I need to do...
Uh, how much is this?
Eight?
What's that?
Eight, eight, eight, eight, eight.
Yep.
So eight hundred and, uh...
Eight hundred twelve.
Get rid of everything.
So we need 500.
That's, uh, seven hundred.
Eight hundred and twelve.
Uh, that's ten.
And that's...
eight hundred and twelve.
And this was...
Oh boy.
Okay, wait, what?
What about the last one?
Let's make coffee.
Transform.
Wait, what does this do?
Oh no!
Of course it would do that.
Uh, why did I click that?
I think I had it wrong anyway.
There was something wrong.
Like, I needed a last one.
I didn't do carbon.
Okay, hold on a minute.
Get all these back.
So we needed...
What was it?
One thousand four hundred and...
Let me just confirm.
Is that four?
It is.
One thousand four hundred and five.
One thousand two hundred.
Three hundred four hundred and five.
Gold.
Okay, it ends up in the green.
That's good, I guess.
Okay, yeah, see, now it lights up one.
Okay, yeah.
So last...
I think I did gold twice because it still saved the last one I had down here.
Okay, now we need to do...
What was it?
Eight hundred and twelve?
Silver.
Five, six, seven, eight hundred and...
Twelve.
And that's silver.
Go.
Nice.
And now we can do carbon.
Which is...
Four... forty... nine?
Forty-six.
That's not a lot.
Forty-six, huh?
One, two, three... forty...
Six.
And that is carbon.
Boom.
That was not a lot.
That was just a tiny smidgen of carbon.
But it's apparently just what the doctor ordered.
Let's see.
Oh, it's forming the key!
I didn't even realize the mold.
Oh, yes, dude.
But wait, that doesn't...
Oh, we will have to make...
different combinations for the different doors.
Or put in a different mold, maybe?
Because all the doors on the different floors have different key molds or key slots.
Okay, okay.
What about this door, though?
Why is it...
I thought it would somehow open that, but...
This is for the fairy gate.
Let's see.
Yep.
Look at that.
And I guess now that I used it, it's gone up here.
Ooh.
Yes!
Man, what am I going to find up there?
God?
God is on up high?
Oh.
Wow.
Oh, that's pretty.
What are these stairs?
Oh, my God.
What's that?
It's raining up here.
Oh, we got a new language?
Yes!
Oh, wow.
Wind?
Is that an equation?
Wait.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho.
I get it.
I understand everything that we're seeing here.
You ready?
This is Devotee.
Oh, nice.
There it is.
And look, there's no more space for another bookmark.
This has to be the last one.
Devotee.
This is...
Oh, what about the...
Wait a minute.
So, Devotee...
Let me just think.
Devotee, warrior, bard, alchemist.
Whatever this place is.
I don't know if this counts as a floor.
Oh, God, I don't know.
But, the fact that...
Someone was like, oh, this is here.
But no, no, no, sorry.
It's crossed it out and then it's here.
I mean, this has to mean equals.
Alchemists equals bards because they're brothers.
But if this is crossed out, does that mean this is alchemist or brother?
Or, I mean, alchemist or bard?
Oh,
I don't know.
Oh, wait, Devotee?
Warrior?
Wait a minute.
Is it listing the civilizations?
Devotee at the bottom, warrior, bards, and alchemists.
What is this glyph over here, though?
Maybe, actually, maybe this is not equals because why would it be here?
Oh, maybe all men are equal.
Oh, God, I don't know.
Does this count as a floor up here?
I don't know.
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe the colors signify something.
Why is this red?
Oh, maybe the yellow stuff is what was originally written on this.
By the way, this music is great.
Something sad about it.
But the yellow stuff was made with this plaque in mind.
And then someone came and graffitied the red stuff on top.
That's the difference, or the reason for the difference in color.
You can also see it's more shoddy, you know?
This is very pristine.
Honestly, I'm just going to write it.
I think this is an order.
Alchemist, Bard, Warrior, and Devotee.
And this, though, I don't know about that.
Okay, if that's the case, Alchemist, something, this.
I could totally see this meaning equals because there's a double meaning there, you know?
All men are equal, and it also has a mathematical meaning.
Which I think is what they're trying to do here.
But in that case, what would Alchemist equal?
Yeah, I'm not sure about...
Oh god, I'm actually not sure about any of this.
Maybe I'm completely wrong about this being Devotee to begin with.
This looks like a symbol for naught.
Oh, man.
I think I'm just going to leave it for now.
I'm going to leave these guesses in even though they may be wrong.
Just for context later.
So I remember...
Oh, okay, we got something.
The tower.
Cenar.
Oh, I don't know.
Humans.
Oh, plural?
Singular.
Equals?
Everyone is equal?
Oh, dude, this is tough.
I have no good guesses for this.
At all.
The reason I wanted to call these warriors to begin with was because the warriors came looking for the tower, remember?
They were sort of on the sides of the tower in an earlier drawing we found.
Alchemist, Bard, Warrior, Devotee.
Would that make sense to write up here?
Maybe this sign is tower.
Does that make sense?
We would have something and then tower at the end or Cenar.
Maybe all cultures of Cenar.
I don't know.
Devotee.
You know what?
I think let's just call this...
Let's call that tower.
I think it goes over here.
But I don't want to guess, of course.
The fact that there's only one glyph in any of these levels here could suggest that this doesn't specify a specific culture.
But it just symbolizes the tower that's being shown here.
This is the tower.
Or Cenar.
One of those two.
I could imagine this meaning Cenar, actually.
That would be a nice thing to do.
This could mean humans.
Just all humans.
If we do that...
Also, if this was equals, these two lines would be the same length, right?
They're not?
So...
Yeah, I don't know.
Let's just call it humans.
Human.
Or man.
Human?
Why would someone cross this out and write that?
And then write this afterwards?
Huh.
There's a moon.
Clouds.
I mean, it could just move on.
Yeah, I think I got most of this shit wrong.
We gotta erase this.
I don't think this is right.
Tower is a good guess, I think.
I'm gonna write equals here as well.
This... I don't know about that.
Let's look at the shapes of these things.
Here we have a Tetris piece and a line.
Okay.
Not sure that means anything.
Okay, let's leave this for now, because I am completely clueless.
We can go two directions here.
God, I love the look of this place.
Beautiful colors, too.
Let's go up here.
Also, what is this thing over here?
Nothing sings like a kilovolt.
Unique pitch.
Nothing else in nature quite like it.
This is high-tech shit!
Look at that monitor!
These are aliens.
There's a door over there.
To a place.
So this is a place, maybe?
Place?
I'm putting a star, because I'm not sure about that.
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
Let me look at this... monitor.
Someone's riding a horse.
Through a field?
Okay.
Maybe he's saying greetings.
Oh, I don't know what you're saying.
This is a good guess for a greeting, though.
Solitude.
Company.
Loneliness.
Isolation.
Community.
That makes sense.
Maybe that mural said something along the lines of...
At first, everyone was isolated.
But then we brought them together, right?
Like this, into a community.
I'm gonna write sonar here.
I don't know what else you're saying, man.
Look at this.
There's that symbol again.
It could mean power.
What the hell are they doing?
Are they controlling everyone?
Mind control facility.
Look at that monitor, too.
Someone walking through the woods.
That monitor's broken.
This is disturbing shit.
What the fuck, dude?
The fact that this symbol is there...
Oh...
I don't know.
Keep going.
There's so many of them.
What are you saying?
You're disappointed by something.
You're sad.
The same two words.
The last one changed.
And
the rest of the words we know about already.
Honestly, I think...
This means I.
This could mean you.
The way they're sort of opposite, that would make sense to me.
And if someone starts a sentence by saying the same thing twice like this...
It sounded like they were tired, right?
I...
If that is indeed I, it could mean I...
Or you looking for a tower?
I don't know.
Look at that.
That's civilization.
That's cars on a road.
What the fuck?
Yeah, sorry.
I don't understand what you're saying.
And how am I welcome here?
How am I not being kicked out?
Zoom terminal?
No?
What is this?
Eh?
Oh my god, I'm being overwhelmed.
I have no idea what's happening.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Man, human.
Key.
Wait, why are these connect... Wait.
Oh, okay, okay, I see.
That's cool.
Seek, want.
I'm guessing these have to mean the same thing?
Me.
See, I think that means me.
And if that's the case, key.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah, but wait, wait, wait.
Why is that not... We may have to change this one too.
Wait, me?
Can I rotate... No, I can't rotate that either.
Oh, so these have to be up here?
Me, me.
Me, me, me.
May create... Oh, but this is talk.
Key, key, that's good.
Do we have a key on this circle?
We don't.
I think this means key.
Oh, but this is talk and create.
That doesn't work.
Me.
Maybe I'm not supposed to align the same words.
Maybe I'm supposed to make sentences out of this.
I don't know.
Maybe the concentric circles need to... No, actually, that doesn't make any sense.
Huh, make, create.
If that was over there... Oh!
Okay, so it is aligning the same words.
That's sick.
Ooh, that was a nice help.
Let's see.
Me, talk.
I was right about this.
Talk, key.
Actually looks like a key, if you look at it.
Seek.
Man, human.
Okay.
May create.
Gotcha.
Very cool.
Rosetta Stone, but the modern version.
The high-tech Rosetta Stone.
I kind of want to go back now and see if I can't decipher the beginning.
I have a feeling I'm right.
Right on the nose with community and isolation.
Because all these communities were isolated in this tower, right?
That's got to be an element to this.
Let's see this again.
Towers in R.
Ah, but now we have a word for human, so that one is wrong.
That's man-human.
So this one is... You know what?
Let's call it equals again.
Okay, so is there anything on here that would indicate isolation?
Or community?
This could mean community.
If this is community, what is isolation?
This is not necessarily a place, by the way.
This could mean power.
Because it supplied power to the terminals the people were using.
Maybe?
I don't know.
Power?
Hmm.
Yeah, I'm still puzzled here.
Something...
Let's look at the actual glyphs themselves.
So if this is me, this has to mean you.
It has to be.
And this is the tower.
I think, at least.
Can we spot any other...
Okay, so this means seek.
This is also sort of a cross.
A verb.
Right?
Then we have...
A situation where there's a line and then something else.
Yeah, this is also sort of a cross, right?
A .K.A.
a verb.
It fits.
Straight lines.
Talk.
Oh, that's a verb, too.
And that doesn't look like a cross at all.
Damn.
Maybe I can't do this.
I'm not confident with that anymore.
Ooh, man.
I don't know.
Could anything in this indicate community?
This, probably, right?
In fact, I don't believe in the equals thing.
Community.
Something about loneliness, isolation, or singular.
What could that represent here?
Maybe it's saying something along the lines of, Apes together strong, you know?
I don't know.
If we all come together, we'll be much stronger.
We'll be more powerful.
So why is this crossed out?
What does that mean?
Not?
Could mean not.
Crossing it out, putting this.
So this symbol here is the same as this symbol here.
Oh, God, this is...
really tough.
What are they trying to say here?
So this has to be Tower, right?
Because of the fact that we have this.
I am so sure, in fact, I'm going to put that in right now.
That's that one.
Now, we got two other things.
If we assume community and loneliness or isolation, could that work in a sentence up here?
Something?
The Tower?
Actually, we should also open our minds to the possibility that they could be writing everything in reverse.
You know, so they could be saying the Tower was isolated at first.
But I know I'm definitely, you know, extrapolating from nothing here.
But just by using logic, we should use those...
glyphs that represent these drawings, and try to make meaning of it here, right?
That's the whole point.
I cannot look at this as an equation!
Fuck!
It's so difficult for me to not see that as an equation.
I'm too math-pilled.
But it's probably not.
This is a sentence.
Ah, fuck!
I'll move on.
Let's go down here.
Also, my rope is getting all wet.
What are you saying?
Talk to me.
What are you looking at?
Someone walking in the grass, and then walking on the beach.
The Tower is fucked.
Hello.
Or maybe he's saying bye.
That couldn't mean bye as well, right?
Given context?
Also, your mask is very disturbing.
It looks to me like you're crying.
Similar to how God is crying right now, with the rain.
The Tower is...
not what it used to be.
But it's only two words.
I don't know what you're saying.
I'm sorry.
I learned a new word.
I think that could mean...
Ah, no.
I don't want to guess.
I have no clue.
No clue what that could mean.
You!
Your terminal is broken!
What are you looking at?
Goddammit.
Okay, okay, so this terminal is broken, and there's no...
Uh... simple like this next to it.
And look up here.
Terminal... Oh no, never mind.
There's no X on this one either.
Okay, I don't know then.
Damn.
This has to mean Power Station or something.
Phew.
This place is making me depressed.
Oh!
Bet we can't do it yet, though.
Because we don't know the language.
Oh!
The bar is trying to communicate with...
someone, but that person isn't here.
We did all the terminals, though.
And would you look at that?
The flower is complete.
What's up here?
Yo, look at that.
Very interesting architecture.
Lovely background.
So I'm back here now.
Let me click there.
What is that?
Key.
Unlock.
Door.
That makes sense.
Keys do, in fact, unlock doors.
Key.
Unlock.
Well, I don't really have a...
word for that.
Shit.
I guess I'll be back.
Oh my God!
They're playing video games!
It's a multiplayer match!
That's awesome!
Who's winning?
Huh?
Guys, can I join?
Man, this civilization here has transcendence.
They've reached the next stage of evolution.
Just sit down all day in VR goggles and play video games.
I love it.
Ooh, this is big.
Here we go.
Let's see.
Up and great.
Door.
Do we have any more for you?
We do?
Well, that one is definitely you.
So this needs to be here.
We know that.
Boom.
You, you, you.
Ava, wait, if I rotate any of the others, then we're kind of fucked.
That makes sense.
Go pass.
Ooh, that one is not good, though.
Maybe I'm wrong on this.
Maybe this is not you.
Door.
Okay, so this one needs to be down there.
Whoops.
There's no way around that.
Or this one needs to be up there, of course.
It could be either or.
Oh yeah, because we have nothing here.
Yep.
Amazing.
This is an interesting way of unlocking the glyphs.
Very cool.
You go help at the door up there where you die.
No, I'm kidding.
But okay.
Interesting.
We're learning new things.
You know what?
Let's take a break here.
Hold on a minute.
Did I come from here?
I did.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's take a break here.
I'll see you in the next episode.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.